<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rodrigo Araujo Soria</title>
    <link>https://rodaraujo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rodrigo Araujo Soria</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 19:26:31 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rodaraujo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rodaraujo.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:32:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodaraujo.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there, I’m a Game Designer, Web Designer specialized in Project Managing and a former Digital Marketing Planner from Guatemala.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://rodaraujo.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 09:50:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodaraujo.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Technology and Expertise Day-to-Day Comfort: Unreal Engine Blender Unreal Motion Graphics HTML, CSS, JavaScript WordPress Drupal Hugo Static Site Generator Experience with: Laravel C++ PHP AutoCAD Adobe Creative Cloud Affinity Designer Work Experience 2014 – Today Project Manager BTO Software BTO Software (2014 – Today) Managed web development projects for the creation of new websites and web applications. Managed customer communication and requests. Web and UI/UX preliminary design for websites and web applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard Shelled</title>
      <link>https://rodaraujo.com/projects/hardshelled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 14:40:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodaraujo.com/projects/hardshelled/</guid>
      <description>Landing Page is full HTML in /layouts/projects/hardshelled-baseof.html
This file contains metadata used for HTML, SEO and Hugo content views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AudioRetrato</title>
      <link>https://rodaraujo.com/projects/audioretrato/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 12:00:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodaraujo.com/projects/audioretrato/</guid>
      <description>AudioRetrato is a compilation of interviews in Spanish with people who have had uncommon life experiences. Every person in the world has something that makes them different from others, and this makes their point of view in live unique. Each episode seeks to understand the unique point of view of the interviewees with the objective of discovering their convictions and motivations that led them to extraordinary life experiences. You can listen to it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TankBot</title>
      <link>https://rodaraujo.com/projects/tankbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 14:40:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodaraujo.com/projects/tankbot/</guid>
      <description>TankBot is a 3D video game prototype that looks to imitate the exciting feel of 2D Shoot ’em up games like Contra and Metal Slug. All assets (3D models, sounds, animations, textures, etc.) in the game are placeholders to exemplify the game experience.
Unlike many other third person shooters with cover up mechanics, TankBot rewards forward aggressive play by boosting the player during combat. If you manage to destroy an enemy robot, you’ll get tools to destroy the rest!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
